<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tester_cardview3</string>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>
            Para 1
        </item>
        <item>
            Para 2
        </item>
        <item>
            Para 3
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="courses">
        <item>Appetizer</item>
        <item>Entree</item>
        <item>Drinks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item1">
        <item>Yam</item>
        <item>Orange potato</item>
        <item>$0.99</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item2">
        <item>Squash</item>
        <item>Why do they call it this anyway?</item>
        <item>$2.99</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item3">
        <item>Asparagus</item>
        <item>Floppy green spears of nutrion</item>
        <item>$1.50</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="content">
        <item>
            ThumbsUp Tutoring embraces the tech community by setting computer literacy as the objective.
        Once this objective is accomplished, we teach the fundamentals of major industries such as web,
        mobile, cloud and video games. If you have programming experience but want to learn more about
        a specific industry, such as cloud computing, ThumbsUp is ready to start where you are and
        bring you to the next level.
        </item>
        <item>
            ThumbsUp offers two types of curriculum: structured and organic. The structured curriculum
        is a preset order of topics that methodically teach the pupil the fundamentals of
        programming. The organic curriculum is more pupil based and adapts to what the pupil
        already knows and what technologies they are interested in learning.
        </item>
        <item>
            There is a lot to learn about in the tech industry and software development. So much, in
        fact, that it is more important to let the pupil’s innate desire be a compass for what
        technologies are learned next. ThumbsUp strives to strengthen the pupil’s computer literacy
        so that eventually they are able to take on the next challenge themselves.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
